Contact

B2 L1 Ph2 De Lima Subd. Brgy. Ibaba City of Santa Rosa Laguna, Philippines 09761479600 (Home) sal8gelacio@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/samuel-allengelacio (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

HTML

MySQL

AngularJS

Certifications

Secure Full Stack Developer Programming

MOST COMPREHENSIVE SEARCH ENGINE OPTIMIZATION CHECKLIST ON FUNDAMENTAL

Introduction to Git

MEAN for FSD Development: Introduction to the MEAN Stack

FSD Front-end Development: Features of HTML5 & CSS3

Samuel Allen Gelacio

Full Stack Developer

Santa Rosa City, Calabarzon, Philippines

Summary

He is a graduate student of Polytechnic University of the Philippines. He has few job experiences like Appointment Setter for a BPO company for 11 months where he answers outbound and inbound calls for Foreign Insurance Companies. A Front-End Developer for Exceed Web Solutions for 9 months wherein, he implements designs given by the web designers. A past intern and currently a Junior Automation Developer at CGI where he is one of the developers responsible for developing and maintaining a website for the company. He has good communication skills and an average knowledge of programming. He is quite familiar with languages such as C, C++, C#, Java, CSS, HTML and JavaScript. Feel free to message him about anything.

Experience

CGI

1 year

Junior Consultant August 2022 - Present (8 months)

Taguig, National Capital Region, Philippines

His duties will primarily revolve around building software by writing code, as well as modifying software to fix errors, adapt it to new hardware, improve its performance, or upgrade interfaces. He will also be involved in directing system testing and validation procedures, and also working with customers or departments on technical issues including software system design and maintenance.

Junior Automation Developer April 2022 - July 2022 (4 months)

Taguig, National Capital Region, Philippines

He is a Junior Automation Developer Intern at CGI Philippines Taguig Office, he worked on 2 projects while in his Internship months. His duties working as a junior developer revolved around building software by writing code, as well as modifying software to fix errors, adapt it to new hardware, or upgrade

interfaces. He also helped on testing and making mockup designs for the website projects that he was assigned to.

Exceed Web Solutions
Web Developer
February 2021 - October 2021 (9 months)

He worked as a part timer Frontend Developer in this company Exceed Web Solutions. He implements designs that were given by the designers so that the design will be viewable in website form. he like to code stuffs and him working here helped him to handle more workloads and more knowledge about CSS, HTML and JavaScript. Working in this company showed him new knowledges and help him see how workloads are distributed to each employee.

ProtelCongo Appointment Setter March 2019 - January 2020 (11 months) Calabarzon, Philippines

He worked as an Appointment Setter in Protel Company for almost 11 months as full time while studying at PUP Santa Rosa Campus to suffice his academic needs. His job is to do outbound calls then lead the hot contacts to the local agent of and Insurance company that was assigned to me. He also answers some inbound calls if they scheduled callbacks for that Insurance Company.

Education

Polytechnic University of the Philippines

Bachelor of Science - BS, Information Technology · (June 2018 - October 2022)